This is unbelievable!
It's been half an hour.
If this was a cartoon,
you'd look like a ham about now.
There's the waitress.
Excuse me!
- Hello, miss?
- It's Phoebe!
Okay, will that be all?
Wait, wait.
What are you doing here?
I was over there...
...then you said, "Excuse me, miss."
So now I'm here.
How come you're working here?
Because it's close to where I live,
and the aprons are really cute.
Can we start over?
Okay, great.
I'm gonna be over here.
The One With the Two Parts - Part I
I don't know if he's testing me
or just acting out...
...but my monkey is out of control!
He keeps erasing
the messages on my machine.
Supposedly by accident.
Yeah, I've done that.
And three days in a row, he got
to the newspaper before I did...
...and peed all over the crossword!
I've never done that.
And then last night, I don't know what he did, but there were capers everywhere.
Allright now look at her and tell me she
doesn't look exactly like her sister.
I'm saying I see a difference.
They're twins.
I don't care.
Phoebe's Phoebe. Ursula's hot.
You know that thing
when we talk about things?
Let's not do that anymore.
Hey, Pheebs.
Guess who we saw today?
Oh, fun!
- Liam Neeson.
- No.
Morley Safer.
The woman who cuts my hair!
This could be a really long game.
Your sister, Ursula.
Oh, really?
She works at that place...
Riff's. Yeah, I know.
You do? She said you guys
haven't talked in years.
So is she fat?
Not from where I was standing.
Where were you standing?
Pheebs, so you guys
just don't get along?
It's mostly just dumb
sister stuff, you know?
Everyone always thought of her
as the pretty one.
She was the first to walk...
...even though I did it
later that same day.
To my parents, by then it was,
"Yeah, what else is new?"
I'm sorry. I've gotta go.
I've got Lamaze class.
And I've got earth science,
but I'll catch you in gym?
Is this just gonna be you and Carol?
Susan will be there too.
We've got dads, we've got lesbians.
The whole parenting team.
Isn't that gonna be weird?
It might have been at first...
...but now I'm comfortable
with the situation.
Ross, that's my jacket.
I know.
We're the Rostens.
I'm J.C. And he's Michael.
And we're having a boy and a girl.
Good for you!
Alrighty, next?
I'm Ross Geller.
And that's my boy in there.
And this is Carol Willick,
and this is Susan Bunch.
Susan is Carol's...
Who's next?
Sorry I didn't get it, Susan is...?
- Susan is Carol's friend.
- Life partner.
Like buddies.
Like lovers.
You know how close women can get.
- Susan and I live together.
- I was married to her.
- Carol, not me.
- It's a little complicated.
- But we're fine.
- Absolutely.
So, twins!
That's like two birds.
- To you too, Helen!
Nina Bookbinder is here to see you.
Okay, send her in.
- Come on in.
- You wanted to see me?
I was just going over your data.
You've been postdating
your Friday numbers.
Which is bad, because...?
It throws my WENUS out of whack.
Excuse me?
WENUS.
Weekly Estimated
Net Usage Statistics.
Right. Gotcha, gotcha.
Won't happen again. I wouldn't
want to do anything to hurt your...
...WENUS.
It's not just that she's cute, okay?
It's just that...
...she's really, really cute.
It doesn't matter. You don't dip
your pen in the company ink.
God, even I know that, and I'm pretty much unemployable.
Ross.
Your little creature's
got the remote again.
Marcel, give Rossy the remote.
Marcel!
Marcel, you give Rossy
the remote right now!
You give Rossy the remote...
- Great.
- Relax. I'll fix it.
Oh, cool.
Urkel...
...in Spanish is Urkel.
How did he do this?
Is leaving the Christmas lights up...
...your plan to keep us
merry all year long?
Someone was supposed to take
them down around New Year's...
...but obviously someone forgot!
Someone was supposed to write:
"Rach, take down the lights"
and put it on the refrigera...
How long has that been there?
Where you been?
I went to Riff's. I think Ursula likes me.
All I ordered was coffee.
She brought me a tuna melt
and four plates of curly fries.
Score.
She is so hot!
Okay, before you do
anything Joey-like...
...you might want to run it by...
Pheebs?
Would it be okay
if I asked out your sister?
Why? Why would you
want to do that? Why?
So that if we went out on a date,
she'd be there.
Well, I mean, I'm not
my sister's, you know...
...whatever.
And I mean, it's true,
we were one egg once.
But, you know,
we've grown apart, so...
I don't know. Why not?
Cool. Thanks.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Do you wanna watch
"Laverne y Shirley"?
Sorry.
Sorry I'm late.
Where's Carol?
Stuck at school.
Some parent-teacher thing.
You can go.
I'll get the information.
No, I think I should stay.
We should both know what's going on.
Oh, good.
This will be fun.
We're gonna start with some basic
third-stage breathing exercises.
Mommies, get on your back.
And, coaches, you should be
supporting Mommy's head.
- What?
I'm supposed to be the mommy?
Okay, I'm gonna play
my sperm card one more time.
I have to miss out on the coaching
training because I'm a woman?
So what do you propose to do?
- I'll flip you for it.
- Flip me for it?
Heads, heads, heads!
On your back, Mom!
All right, Mommies, take
a nice, deep, cleansing breath.
Good.
Now imagine your vagina is opening...
...like a flower.
Mr. Dee! How's it going, sir?
It's been better.
The Annual Net Usage
Statistics are in.
It's pretty ugly.
We haven't seen an ANUS
this bad since the '70s.
What's it mean?
We'll be laying off people.
I know I was late last week.
I slept funny and my hair was snarly.
Not you.
Relax.
Ever have to fire anyone?
No, but that's not a problem sir, that's why my name's on the door.
By the way, do you know when I'm getting my name on the door?
I don't know. I... put it in "the thing".
So... who's it gonna be?
Nina...
Nina.
Nina?
Ninaaaa....
Are you okay?
Yes. Yes, I am.
Listen, the reason that
I called you in here today was...
Please don't hate me.
What?
Would you like
to have dinner sometime?
So Pheebs, what do you want
for your birthday?
What I really want is for my mom
to be alive and enjoy it with me.
Let me put it this way.
Anything from Crabtree & Evelyn?
Bath salts would be nice!
Good.
What is this place?
You're cold, I have to pee,
and there's coffee.
How bad could it be?
I think we have an answer.
What's she doing here?
This could be God's way
of telling us to eat at home.
- Think she got fired at Riff's?
- No, we were there last night.
She kept bringing swordfish.
Are you gonna go...?
I'll wait until we order.
It's her, right?
It looks like her.
Excuse me?
Hi, it's us!
Right. And it's me!
So you're here too?
As much as you are.
Your turn.
We know what we want.
That's good.
- Two caffe lattes.
- And some biscotti cookies.
Good choice.
It's definitely her.
I can't believe you.
You still haven't told that girl
she doesn't have a job?
You still haven't taken down
the Christmas lights.
Congratulations! I think you found
the world's thinnest argument.
Trying to find the right moment.
That shouldn't be so hard,
now that you're dating.
"Sweetheart, you're fired. But how
about a quickie before I go to work?"
Once you're inside,
you don't have to knock anymore.
I'll get it.
Hi, Mr. Heckles.
You're doing it again.
We're not doing anything.
We're just sitting around
talking quietly.
I can hear you through the ceiling.
My cats can't sleep.
You don't even have cats.
I could have cats.
Goodbye, Mr. Heckles.
We'll try to keep it down.
Phoebe, can you do me a favor?
Try this on to make sure it fits.
My first birthday present!
Oh, this is really...
No no no, it's for Ursula.
I just figured, you know, size-wise.
Sure. Yeah.
Okay, it fits.
Are you seeing her again?
Yep, Ice Capades.
This is serious.
I've never known you to pay money
for any kind of "capade".
I don't know. I like her.
She's different.
There's something about her...
That you like.
We get it. You like her.
Phoebe, I asked you
and you said it was okay.
Well, maybe now it's not okay.
Well, maybe now I'm not okay
with it not being okay.
Knit, good woman.
Knit! Knit!
And that's the Chrysler Building
right there.
Mr. Douglas.
Cool tie.
She's still here.
Yes. Yes, she is.
Didn't I memo you?
After I let her go, I got a call
from her psychiatrist, Dr. Flanen...
...Dr. Flanan, Dr. Flan.
And he informed me that
she took the news rather badly.
In fact, he mentioned
the word "frenzy".
She seems so...
Oh, no, no.
Nina? She's...
In fact, if you asked her now...
...she'd have no recollection
of being fired at all.
That's unbelievable.
And yet believable.
So I decided not to fire her again...
...until I'm sure she will be
of no threat to herself or others.
I see. You never really know what's
going on inside a person's head.
Well, I guess that's why
they call it psychology, sir.
The sound Mom and Dad
will never forget.
For this, after all,
is the miracle of birth.
Lights, please.
And that's having a baby.
Next week is our final class.
Susan, go deep.
It's impossible.
It's just impossible.
What is, honey?
What that woman...
...did.
I am not doing that!
It'll have to stay in, that's all.
Everything will be the same.
- It'll just stay in.
- Carol, honey.
- Everything will be all right.
- What do you know?
No one's saying to you,
"Hi, is that your nostril?
Mind if we push
this pot roast through it?!"
Carol, sweetie.
Cleansing breath.
I know it's frightening.
But big picture:
The birth part is just one day...
...and when it's over, we'll all
be parents for the rest of our lives.
I mean, that's what
this is all about, right?
Ross?
Ross.
I'm gonna be a father.
- This is just occurring to you?
- I knew I was having a baby.
I just never realized
the baby was having me.
You're gonna be great.
How could you say that?
I can't even get Marcel
to stop eating the bathmat.
How am I gonna raise a kid?
You know, some scientists
are now saying...
...that monkeys and babies
are actually different.
You might wonna look into it...
- Where are you going?
- Out.
With...?
Yes!
Alright, can I just ask you one question?
Have you two, you know,
like, you know?
You know?
Yet?
Well, not that it's any
of your business, but...
...no, we haven't. Okay?
You meant sex, right?
- Do you have a sec?
- Sure, Nina. What's up?
I don't know, for the past couple of days,
people have been avoiding me...
...and giving me strange looks.
Oh, well, maybe that's because...
...they're jealous of us.
Maybe.
But that doesn't explain why
they keep taking my scissors.
Well, maybe that's because
you're getting a big raise!
- I am?
- Sure. Why not?
Oh, my God!
You're amazing!
Oh, you don't know.
Helen, make sure we do the paperwork
on Miss Bookbinder's raise.
You still want me to send her
psychological profile to personnel?
Helen drinks.
Will you marry me?
- After the proposal, I kind of unreveled.
Right, because you were really in control up untill then.
- Yeah, well, I ended up telling her everything.
- Oh, how'd she take it?
Pretty well.
Except for the stapler thing.
Little tip. If you're ever
in a similar situation...
...never, ever leave
your hand on the desk.
Okay, I think I get how to do this.
Can we turn this off?
Can we make them go away?
Because I can't watch.
They're gone.
Are you all right?
Yeah. It's just this whole
stupid Ursula thing.
Okay Pheebs, can I ask...?
So he's going out with her.
Is it really so terrible?
Yeah.
I mean, I'm not saying
she's evil or anything.
She's just, you know,
she's always breaking my stuff.
When I was 8, I wouldn't let her
have my Judy Jetson thermos...
...so she threw it under the bus.
And then when I was twelve and she broke my colar bone.
Alright, she didn't mean to do it.
But I think it still counts.
And then there's Randy Brown...
...who was like...
Have you ever had a boyfriend
who was your best friend?
Well, but that's what he was for me.
And she, you know,
kind of stole him away...
...and then broke his heart.
And then he wouldn't
even talk to me anymore.
He didn't want to be around anything
that looked like either one of us.
I mean, I know Joey's not
my boyfriend or my thermos...
...or anything, but...
- You won't lose him.
- You gotta talk to Joey.
Yeah, okay.
He doesn't know this stuff.
If he knew how you felt...
He's falling in love with her.
They've been going out a week.
They haven't even slept together yet.
I mean, that's not serious.
May we help you?
What are you doing? It's freezing!
Would you come inside?
No, no, no.
You wanted me to take them down...
...so I'm taking them down, okay?
Rachel!
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Mr. Heckles?
Mr. Heckles,
could you help me, please?
This is just the kind of thing
I was talking about.
My friend was taking down
our Christmas lights...
...and she fell off the balcony
and may have broken her ankle.
My God, you still have
your Christmas lights up?
Fill this out and bring it back to me.
Here you go.
All right.
Name...
...address...
Okay, are you currently on any medication?
No.
Oh, wait wait yes!
Blistex.
Ah, NO!
In case of emergency, call...?
You.
Really?
Oh, that is so sweet!
Oh, gosh. I love you.
Okay, insurance?
Yeah, check it.
Definitely gonna want some of that!
You don't have insurance?
Why? How much is this gonna cost?
I have no idea, but X-rays alone could be
a couple hundred dollars!
- What'll we do?
- There's not much we can do.
Unless I use yours.
Now wait a second.
Who did I just put as my
"in case of emergency" person?
That's insurance fraud.
All right then, forget it.
Might as well just go home.
- Okay, come here. I hate this.
- Thank you. I love you.
I'm gonna need
a new set of these forms.
Why?
I am really an idiot!
I was filling out my friend's form...
...and instead of putting
her information...
...I put mine.
You are an idiot.
Yep, that's me.
I am that stupid.
I had a dream that I was
playing football with my kid.
That's nice.
No, no. With him.
I'm on this field,
and they hike me the baby.
I've gotta do something because the
Tampa Bay team's coming right at me!
Tampa Bay's got a terrible team.
Right, but...
...it is just me and the baby,
so I'm thinking they can take us.
And so, I...
...I just heave it downfield!
What are you, crazy?
That's a baby!
He should take the sack?
Anyway...
...suddenly I'm downfield.
And I realize that I'm the one
who's suppose to catch him, right?
Only I know I'm not gonna
get there in time.
So I am running and I'm running...
...and that is when I woke up.
See, I am so not ready
to be a father.
Hey, you're gonna be fine.
You're one of the most caring,
responsible men in North America.
You're gonna make a great dad.
Yeah, Ross. You and the baby
just need better blocking.
Have you ever been to the
Rainbow Room? Is it expensive?
Only if you order stuff.
I'm taking Ursula tonight.
It's her birthday.
- What about Phoebe's birthday?
- When's that?
Tonight.
Man, what are the odds
of that happening?
You take your time.
There it is!
So,  what are you gonna do?
What can I do? I don't want
to screw it up with Ursula.
And your friend, Phoebe?
If she's my friend, she'll understand.
Wouldn't you guys?
If you tried that on my birthday...
...you'd be staring at
the business end of a hissy fit.
An added pinch of saffron
makes all the difference.
Monica?
Yes?
Yes, she is.
This is my friend, Rachel.
Hi Rachel, I'm Dr. Mitchell.
And I'm his friend, Dr. Rosen.
I'm Okay here.
actually, that's alright.
I don't mind at all, now you can take your break.
Aren't you a little cute
to be a doctor?
Excuse me?
I meant, god, young, young.
I meant young.
Young to be a doctor.
- Good, Rach.
- Thank you.
So he said it was a sprain,
and that was it.
You left out the stupid part.
It's not stupid.
The very cute doctors asked us out
for tomorrow night, and I said yes.
I think it's totally insane.
They work for the hospital.
It's like returning
to the scene of the crime.
- I say we blow off the dates.
- What? Monica, they are cute.
They are doctors. Cute doctors.
Doctors who are cute.
All right, what have
we learned so far?
Oh, God.
Surprise!
What are you doing?
You scared the crap out of me!
- Was that the cake?
- Yeah.
I got a lemon schmush.
Come on.
She'll be here any minute.
I hope it's okay.
"Happy Birthday, Peehee."
Maybe we can make
a "B" out of a rose.
Yeah, we'll just use
our special cake tools.
- What's going on?
- We just...
Surprise!
This is so great!
This was not at all scary.
Oh look, "happy birthday Peehee".
What a strange new nickname.
I like it!
Oh my god!
Hi, everybody. Hi, Betty!
Betty, hi!
You found Betty!
Oh, my gosh! This is so great.
Everybody I love is in the same room.
Where's Joey?
Did you see Betty?
I'll tell you one thing, I wouldn't mind having a piece
of this sun-dried tomato business.
Five years ago, if somebody'd said, "Here's
a tomato that looks like a prune"...
...I'd have said,
"Get out of my office!"
Dad, before I was born,
did you freak out at all?
I'm not freaking out!
I'm just saying...
...if someone had come to me
with the idea...
I'm talking about
the whole baby thing.
Did you ever get this sort of...
...panicky, "Oh, my God, I'm gonna
be a father" kind of a thing?
We just had kids back then. We didn't think about it.
What else could the sun dry? I wonder.
Right, look. Your mother really did the work.
I was busy with the business.
I wasn't around that much.
Is that what this is about?
No, no. I was just wondering.
Cause there's time to make up for that.
We can do stuff together.
You always wanted to go to colonial
Williamsburg. How about we do that?
Thanks, Dad, really.
You know, I just, I just...
I just needed to know...
...when did you start
to feel like a father?
Well, I guess it must have been
the day after you were born.
We were in the hospital room,
your mother was asleep...
...and they brought you in
and gave you to me.
You were this ugly little red thing!
And all of a sudden, you grabbed
my finger with your whole fist...
...and you squeezed it...
...so tight.
And that's when I knew.
So you don't want to go
to Williamsburg?
We can go to Williamsburg.
Eat your fish.
Rachel, the cute doctors are here!
Okay, coming.
Hi, come on in.
Hey, Michael, Jeffrey.
Here, we brought wine.
Look at this. It's from the cellars
of Ernest and Tova Borgnine.
- How could we resist?
- Oh, that's great, look at that!
- So, Monica, how's the ankle?
- It's...
Why don't you tell them?
After all, it is your ankle.
You know, what? It's feeling a lot better.
Thank you.
listen, why don't you guys sit down,
and we'll get you some glasses.
Stat!
Okay, listen, I'm thinking why don't we just
tell them who we really are?
- I mean it'll be fine. I really think it will be fine.
- It will not be fine. We'll get in trouble.
Mnica, would you stop being such a wuss!
A wuss? Excuse me
for living in the real world.
- So?
- So they still seem normal.
That's because they are.
Okay, but you have to admit that every time
we go out with women we meet at the hospital it turns into...
Would you relax?
Take a look around.
There are no pagan altars.
No piles of bones in the corners.
They're fine. Go like this:
I said we are not going to do it, okay?
Sometimes you can be such a big baby!
- I am not a baby.
- Be serious.
- You get uptight...
- You act like a princess.
You know what? You know what?
Every day you are becoming
more and more like your mother.
Excuse me.
Here we go.
This is a great place.
How long have you lived here?
Thanks. I've been here
about six years.
And Rachel moved in a few months ago.
See, I was supposed to get married...
...but I left the guy at the altar.
Yeah, I know
it's pretty selfish, but...
...hey, that's me!
Why don't you try the hummus?
So, Monica, what do you do?
I am a chef at a restaurant uptown.
Good for you.
Yeah, it is.
Mostly because I get to boss people
around, which I just love to do.
Well, this hummus is great.
God bless the chickpea.
Oh, God!
I am so spoiled!
That's it.
I shoplift.
That was years ago and you had no idea that lipstick was in your pocket.
Did I tell you that I think I'm so much cuter than I am?
And have I mentioned that
back in high school...
...I was a cow?
I used to wet my bed.
I use my breasts to get
other people's attention.
We both do that!
Monica and Rachel's apartment.
Just one second.
Rachel, it's your dad.
Hi, Dad.
No, no. It's me.
Listen, Dad,
I can't talk right now.
But there's something...
There's something
I've been meaning to tell you.
Excuse me.
Remember back in freshman year?
Well, Billy Dreskin and I
had sex on your bed.
Daddy...
Daddy, daddy why? Why would I sleep
with Billy Dreskin?
His father tried to put
you out of business!
You are dead!
Hey, Rachel, are these your condoms?
Oh, no. No, that was just Monica.
She's drunk again.
Ah, Pheebs, I don't think scrunchy is a word.
Why not?
If crunchy is a word, why isn't scrunchy?
Well, okay, then I'm using that same argument for fligament.
Ross, he's got the remote again.
Good.
Maybe he can switch it back.
Maybe not.
Okay, daddy, that's the other line.
Okay, no. Not even in my bedroom.
Okay, okay.
Bye-bye.
Hello?
Hold on a second and let me
just check and see if she's here.
It's the woman from the hospital.
There's a problem with the form.
Oh, God, what do we do?
Just find out what they want.
Okay. No, you do it.
Hello. This is Monica.
Yes, we'll be right down.
Thank you.
We forgot to sign one
of the admissions forms.
- You're right, this wasn't worth it.
- Thank you.
Okay, let me just change.
gudje?
- Nautical term.
- Cheating man.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Hey... Hi.
- She still didn't call?
- No.
Trouble?
Your sister stood me up
the other night.
Oh, no. Don't you hate it
when people aren't there for you?
What is that?
Tushy!
- Well, did you try calling her?
- I've been trying for two days.
When I called the restaurant,
they said she was busy.
I can't believe
she's blowing me off!
Excuse me, we had the two chef salads.
No, we havn't had hem yet.
We're still hoping to have them.
Okay.
- Hey.
- Oh.
You got a minute?
Yeah, I'm just working.
I got you a birthday present.
Wow, you remembered!
It's a Judy Jetson thermos.
Right, ike the kind you...
Right.
Oh, I got something for you too.
How'd you know I was coming?
Yeah, twin thing.
I can't believe you did this.
I can't believe you...
...did this!
So what's the deal
with you and Joey?
Oh, right.
He is so great.
But that's over.
- Does he know?
- Who?
Joey. You know, he's really nutsy
about you.
He is? Why?
You got me.
Excuse me...
...doesn't this come
with a side salad?
So are you gonna call him?
- You think he likes me?
- No. Joey.
No, no. He is so smart.
He'll figure it out.
Do you want some chicken?
No, no.
No food with a face, remember?
You have not changed.
Yeah, you too.
Excuse me. My side salad?
The service in here is horrible.
Hi! Remember us?
You just called about needing
a signature on the admissions form?
Well, it turns out
we need a whole new one.
Because, you see...
...I put the wrong name again.
- Because...
- You're that stupid!
I am. I'm that stupid!
And I'm just gonna pay
for this with a check.
Well, you know your insurance will cover that.
Yeah, I know.
I'm just not that bright either.
Mon, I'm sorry about last night what I said.
I don't think you're anything like your mother.
Oh, that's alright. And I don't think you're selfish running out on Berry.
Oh, and I'm sorry that I said you were a cow in high school.
That's okay. I was a cow.
Okay, worst case scenario:
Say you never feel like a father.
Say your son never feels
connected to you as one.
Say all of his relationships
are affected by this.
Do you have a point?
You know, you'd think I would.
What's up with the simian?
It's just a fur ball.
Whose turn is it?
Yours. I got
43 points for "kidney".
No, you got
zero points for "idney".
I had a "K".
Where's my "K"?
You've got to help me!
My monkey swallowed a "K"!
You have to get that animal out of here!
You don't understand, the animal hospital is way across town.
He's choking! I don't know what else to do!
- What's going on?
- Marcel swallowed a Scrabble tile.
Excuse me.
This hospital is for people!
Lady, he is people!
He has a name, okay?
He watches "Jeopardy!"
...he touches himself
when nobody's watching.
Please have a heart.
- I'll take a look at him.
- Thank you.
- Michael!
- Rachel.
- What?
- Monica.
Urs!
What are you doing here? I've been trying to call you.
Listen...
Oh, no no no, don't say "listen". I know that
"listen". I've said that "listen".
I'm sorry.
I don't get it.
What happened?
What about what
you said under the bridge?
Forget about what
I said under the bridge.
I was talking crazy that night.
I was so drunk.
You don't drink.
That's right, I don't.
But I was drunk on you.
But it's not gonna work.
Why? Is it because
I'm friends with Phoebe?
If it was, would you
stop hanging out with her?
No, I couldn't do that.
Then, yeah, it's because of Phoebe.
So you know, it's either her or me.
Then I'm sorry.
You're gonna be
really hard to get over.
I know.
I don't know whether it's just
because we're breaking up or what...
...but you've never
looked so beautiful.
Really?
Pheebs?
He looks so tiny.
- We just got the message.
- Is he okay?
The doctor got the "K" out.
He also found an "M" and an "O".
We think he was trying
to spell out "monkey".
The doctor says he'll be fine.
He's just sleeping now.
So you feel like a dad yet?
No. Why?
Come on, you came through.
You did what you had to do.
That's very "dad".
He's waking up.
Hey, fella.
How you doing?