Hey, how much you give me
to eat this whole jar of olives?
l won't give you anything,
but you'll owe me $2.95.
Done.
l need an atlas!
Why? Do you have a report due?
l have a date with this diplomat
l met while giving free massages...
...outside the U.N. and....
l don't know where his country is.
Okay, let's start with
the free massages at the U.N.
lt's my new thing. l figure,
bodies at peace make peace.
You might just get
the first Nobel Prize in rubbing.
So, what country is this guy from?
There's a G in there.
-Well, where's that?
-ln your atlas.
l don't have an atlas.
But, wait, l do have a globe.
Hold on.
So what's this guy like?
Well, he's very...
...dashing, you know?
And very, very sophisticated.
And he doesn't speak any English...
...but according to his translator
he totally gets me.
Okay, here you go.
What is this?
lt's a globe.
And a pencil sharpener.
People of Earth, surrender.
Giant alien.
Five tiny heads.
Anybody need anything copied?
l'm going to the Xerox place.
No, thanks.
Okay, listen, just give me
anything l can make two of.
lf you don't have anything to copy,
why go there?
Are you going down there to gawk at that
hot girl with the bellybutton ring again?
Yeah. You wanna come?
Yeah.
The One Where
Ross and Rachel Take a Break
Come on, Chloe.
Finish up with your customer first.
Come on, Chloe!
Can l help you?
You know what?
We're having second thoughts
about our copying needs...
...and we'll need a little
more time to think about it.
Chloe, switch with me. There are
some guys here who got a crush on you.
Okay, that hurt us.
Hi, guys. l haven't seen
you since this morning.
Well....
You know.
Hey, what are you guys
doing tomorrow night?
Both of us?
Maybe. Does that scare you?
Relax.
Just lsaac's deejaying at The Philly.
-You should come.
-We'll be there.
Great. l'll see you then.
All right. Rock on.
He says that walking with you makes
this strange city feel like home.
Me too. Although
this city is my home, so....
So that's dumb, what l said.
Don't tell him l said that.
Just you make something up.
Nice. Thank you.
This is me, here.
Your eyes are very pretty.
Thank you very much.
Oh, thank you.
He would like to kiss you.
Okay. You know what,
you don't have to do that now.
No, no, not him!
No, you don't.
The moment's over.
See, there it is, right there.
Wow, it's small.
Yeah, but Sergei said
it took the Germans six weeks...
...to get all the way across it.
-So you had fun?
-Yeah.
Except for-- You know
when you're on a date...
...and you're getting along great...
...but the guy's translator
keeps getting in the way?
No.
-Hey.
What, is Rach in her room?
No, she's still at work,
but she said to call her.
What? ls she gonna cancel
on me again? How could she do this?
Doesn't she know it's our anniversary?
All right, Ross. This is the extent
of my knowledge on the subject.
''Call Rachel.''
What's that on the bottom?
That's my doodle of
a ladybug with a top hat.
She's fancy.
-Hello.
-Hey, honey.
-Hi.
-Hey, how's it going?
Well, kind of having
an underwear emergency.
Oh, yeah? What happened? Someone
scare you? Make you laugh too hard?
There was a disaster in shipping.
l have to get this order in.
Honey, l'm so sorry, but it looks like
l'm gonna be here all night.
What? Well, how about
l come up there?
No. No. No, honey, please. l've got....
l just have too much to deal with.
Anyway, l'm going out
with Sergei again tonight, and....
Could you be the translator's date...
...so that when it's time for our
alone time you two can split off?
You know, he's kind of cute.
Kind of cute like really kind of cute?
Or kind of cute like your friend...
...Spackle-Back Larry?
Hey, don't call him that.
His name is Spackle-Back Harry.
You know, maybe we should get going.
What time did Chloe say to get there?
-1 0:30.
-What time is it now?
4:30.
Yeah, so we'll hang out.
Hey, remember when she brought
up that thing about the three of us?
Yes, vividly.
-She was kidding about that, right?
-Yeah, l think so.
Yeah, l think so.
God, it'd be weird if that situation
presented itself tonight.
Yeah, l mean...
...what would we do?
Dude, l don't know.
-She was kidding.
-Yeah.
She was....
You know, just in case,
we should come up with ground rules.
Yeah. For sure. Okay.
Probably want the first one to be,
''Never open your eyes.''
You know? Because you don't
want to be doing something...
...and then look up, right?
And see something that
you don't want to be seeing.
-You know?
-Yeah.
Good call. Nice.
Hold it! Hold it!
What if my eyes are closed, and...?
And my hand is out there...?
Okay, eyes open at all times.
How do we decide where we...
...you know, each would...
...you know...
-...be?
-Right.
Right. Well, you know,
we could flip for it.
Yeah, l guess. But, like,
what's heads and what's tails?
Well, if you don't know that,
then l don't want to do this with you.
No, no, no.
l am looking at a purchase order right here,
and it clearly states that we ordered...
...the Riviera bikini in a variety
of sizes and colors and--
What does it matter what l'm wearing?
Could l please speak to your supervisor?
Thank you. We're holding.
-Hi.
-Oh, my God!
-What are you doing here?
-Well, you said you couldn't go out, so....
You brought a picnic.
What a boyfriend.
That's it. On Monday,
l start wearing makeup.
Ross, honey, this is very nice,
but l've got a crisis.
Yeah, but l've got couscous!
Honey, l'm sorry,
l know it's our anniversary...
...but l told you on the phone,
l don't have time to stop.
Okay, you don't have to stop.
l'm invisible. l'm not here.
Yeah, but l don't--
Who approved that order?
Well, there is no Mark Robinson
in this office.
-Get me Mark on the phone!
-l love Mark. Do you know Mark?
Yeah.
Let me just check that
with what l've got here.
All right. See, 038 is not the number
for this store. 038 is Atlanta.
Pepper?
-None for me.
-Okay, sorry....
l'm sorry. As l was saying,
the store number is wrong.
And l'm sorry, but that is--
Oh, my God!
Excuse me, l'm sorry. l'll have to call
you back. l've got Shemp in my office.
-What are you doing?
-l'm sorry.
But, hey, somebody's off the phone.
How about a glass of wine...
...by the fire?
l can get it going again.
Ross, you're not listening to me.
l don't have time to stop.
-Come on, you don't have 1 0 minutes?
-l don't have 1 0 minutes!
-Sophie, does she have 1 0 minutes?
-Hey, Ross, l told you l don't!
Don't yell at me, okay? This is
the most l've seen you all week.
Look, l cannot do this right now, okay?
l've got a deadline. Would you
just go home. l'll talk to you later.
-Yeah, but wait--
-Goodbye!
Actually, that's our three-hole punch.
-Hey.
-Hi.
Look, about what happened earlier--
l completely understand.
You were stressed.
l was gonna give you a chance
to apologize to me.
For what? For letting you
throw me out of your office?
You had no right
coming down to my office, Ross.
You do not bring a picnic basket
to somebody's work...
...unless maybe they were
a park ranger.
Well, excuse me for wanting to be
with my girlfriend on our anniversary.
Boy, what an ass am l.
But l told you
l didn't have the time.
Yeah, well, you never have the time.
l don't feel like l even
have a girlfriend anymore.
What do you want from me?
You want me to quit my job so
you can feel like you have a girlfriend?
No, but it would be nice
if you'd realize that it's just a job.
-Just a job?
-Yes.
Do you realize this is the first time in my
life l'm doing something l care about?
This is the first time l'm doing
something l'm actually good at?
l mean, if you don't get that--
l get that. l get that big-time,
and l'm happy for you.
l'm tired of having a relationship
with your answering machine.
-l don't know what to do anymore.
-Well, neither do l!
ls this about Mark?
-Oh, my God!
-Okay, it's not.
Oh, my God! l cannot keep having this
same fight over and over again, Ross.
-You're making this too hard.
-l'm making this too hard?
-Okay, what do you want me to do?
-l don't know. l don't know. Look...
...maybe we should take a break.
Okay. Okay, fine. You're right.
Let's take a break. Let's cool off. Okay.
Let's get some frozen yogurt
or something.
No.
A break from us.
And the advances in collating
in the past five years....
l mean, we just got
in an X-5000, you know?
The X-5000 makes an X-50
look like a T-7 1 .
Hey, it's the dinosaur guy!
-Hi, Ross!
-Hi, Chloe.
l want you to meet
some friends of mine.
This guy's my hero.
He comes in with stuff,
he wants it blown up 400% .
We say, ''We don't do that.''
He says, ''You gotta.''
And you know what?
We did it.
And now anytime anybody wants
400, we just say, ''Let's Ross it!''
And that's the only color
that comes in.
Yo, Chloe. Do you have a quarter
for the condom machine?
What are you doing here? l thought
tonight was your big anniversary dinner.
Yeah, a little change of plans.
We're gonna break up instead.
And l can also speak a little French.
Voulez-vous coucher avec moi ce soir?
Why? What did l say?
Well, you just asked if l wanted
to go to bed with you tonight.
Oh, my God.
No wonder l get such
great service at Cafê Maurice.
Knock, knock, knock, knock.
Hi. Could you please tell Sergei
that l was fascinated...
...by what Boutros Boutros-Ghali
said in the New York Times.
You didn't say
''Boutros Boutros-Ghali.''
Boutros Boutros-Ghali.
He says he was too.
lnteresting.
So l was wondering--
Before you get all talky again...
...could you also please
tell Sergei...
...that l really like his suit.
He said, ''Thank you.''
He thinks you look pretty tonight.
''Your hair, golden like the sun.''
So you're a chef?
l'm also thinking of opening up
my own restaurant.
-Really?
-Could l talk to you behind my menu?
-What are you doing?
-Well, l was having a conversation.
Mischa is so interested in you
that Sergei and l...
...haven't been able to say two words
to each other.
Do you want me to sit here silently
while you three converse?
That would be great.
Thank you.
-Hello?
-Hi. lt's Mark.
-What? ls it my breath?
-No.
Sorry. l just thought
you were somebody else. Hi.
Hi. Look, l was just
gonna leave a message.
lsn't tonight your anniversary dinner?
Well....
-Rach? Are you okay?
-Yeah, l'm fine.
You wanna talk?
I can come over.
No. Really, no. Please. That's okay.
All right. l'm coming,
and l'll bring Chinese food.
Oh, yeah, l'm not hungry.
It's for me.
Okay, bye.
-So, what are you gonna do?
-What can l do?
One person wants to break up,
you break up.
No way. Come on. This is you guys.
Call her and work it out.
Come on. We just had this huge fight.
Don't l have to wait a while?
Hey, this isn't like swimming
after you eat. Pick up the phone!
You know that whole
swimming thing is a myth.
Yeah. Tell that to my uncle Lenny.
Why? What happened to him?
Nothing. He just really
believes in that.
And then we got into this
big, stupid fight.... lt was awful.
l told him he treats me like
a park ranger, something....
And then...
...l told him
l wanted to take a break.
l don't want to take a break.
l'm sorry.
-Egg roll?
-No.
And then l called him,
and he wasn't there.
Well, he's probably just out.
Well, thank you, that's very helpful.
l'm glad you came over.
Hi, it's me.
-Hi. l'm so glad you called.
-Really?
l've been thinking this is crazy.
Don't you think we can work on this?
Hey, what do you wanna drink?
Who's that?
Nobody?
ls it okay if l finish
the apple juice?
ls that Mark?
-Honey, look, he just came over--
-Yeah, got it!
Hey, dinosaur guy.
Look at you, so sad.
-Come dance.
-That's okay. Thanks.
You don't have to smile.
You just have to dance.
l don't feel like dancing.
l feel like having a drink, okay?
Okay. Hey, two beers.
Okay, now we're
just dancing with each other.
And the vet said it was time.
And so from half a world away...
...while my mother
held the phone to his ear...
...l said goodbye to my dog...
...in seven languages.
-Could l have a tissue?
-Yeah, sure.
l just hope you don't accidentally...
...suck it up through your nose
and choke on it.
Sergei would like to apologize
for my behavior tonight.
Well, tell him, ''Apology accepted.''
He's unbelievable.
For the first time in three years,
someone wants to talk to me.
But do you think he would
let me enjoy that? No!
You silly diplomat. Why don't you
learn some English, Sergei.
Excuse me, but isn't he paying
for your dinner?
Hey, the man's dog just died.
l have just resigned my post.
Would you care to accompany
me to the Rainbow Room?
l have diplomatic coupons.
lt would be my pleasure.
My guy has coupons.
Your guy can't even say ''coupons.''
-Plate.
-Plate! Yes! Plate!
Plate.
See, we don't need them.
-Plate?
-Yeah.
l like this song.
Well, you're practically
dancing already.
-Why don't you just do it over here?
-No.
What, are you married?
Because that's okay.
Be home, be home, be home,
be home, be home, be home.
Be home, be home, be home.
You're not home.
Still no smile?
American.
You know, it's a very hard language.
Let's do it again.
[ENGLlSH]