Can't get the monkey off your back?
Then put it in your mouth...
... with Monkeyshine Beer!
Get it, monkey
Get it, get it, monkey
Monkey, monkey
Monkeyshine Beer.
Because it's a jungle out there!
That commercial always
makes me so sad.
But then the guy opens his beer
and girls run at him...
...so everything works out okay.
I meant because the monkey
reminds me of Marcel.
I can see that.
Because they both have those big
brown eyes and the little pouty chin.
And the fact that
they're both monkeys?
I wonder if I did the right thing,
giving him away.
Ross, you had to. He was
humping everything in sight.
My Malibu Barbie will no longer
be wearing white to her wedding.
Remember when he'd borrow your hat...
...and when you got it back,
there'd be monkey raisins in it?
When he did it, it was funny.
When I did it to my boss's hat....
Suddenly, I had this big
"attitude problem."
The One With the Super Bowl
Hey, check it out!
Guess what I got?
Rhythm?
No. My first fan mail!
"Dear Dr. Ramoray:
I love you and would do
anything to have you."
My gosh! "Your not-so-secret
admirer, Erika Ford."
Oh, wait.
"P.S. Enclosed, please find
14 of my eyelashes."
In Crazy World, that means
you're married.
It's not addressed to Days Of Our
Lives. This came to your apartment.
She was in our building.
Oh, my God.
I got my very own stalker!
You are so lucky, I'm gonna share mine.
Joey, remember we talk about good thing and bad thing.
This is a bad thing.
Where are you off to?
There's a paleontology
conference in L.A.
So I figured I'd go and drive down
to the zoo and surprise Marcel.
He will be surprised.
Till he realizes he's a monkey...
...and isn't capable of that emotion.
Phoebe? That really cute guy
is here again.
Okay, so everyone...
... pretend I'm telling you a story
and it's really funny.
So everyone just laugh. Now!
I know, I know!
I'm Rob Donan.
Hi, Rob Donan.
I don't know anything about music,
but I think you're really great.
Anyway, I schedule performers
for children's libraries.
And I was thinking, have you thought
about playing your songs for kids?
I would love to have kids...
...hear me play the songs
that I will write for them.
What do we do for dinner?
We could cook for ourselves.
It's Erika.
My God. The stalker!
Never mind. It's open.
Hitting her with a frying pan
is a good idea.
But we want a backup plan,
just in case she isn't a cartoon!
Let's get out of here!
The one time they're not home!
We'll leave.
When we pass her...
...she won't know me,
because we never met!
That's how radio stars
escape stalkers!
She's coming!
It's me.
This is it.
This is how we're gonna die.
You ready?
Wait, wait, wait!
Erika!
-Mr. Geller?
-Yes, hi.
Dean Lipson, zoo administrator.
You had a question?
I can't find the monkey I donated
last year. He's a capuchin...
...answers to the name Marcel?
I'm afraid I have some bad news.
Marcel has passed on.
Oh, my God. What happened?
He got sick,
and then he got sicker...
...and then he got a little better.
But then he died.
I can't believe this!
I'm sorry, Mr. Geller.
But you know, there's an old saying:
"Sometimes monkeys die."
It's not a great saying...
... but it certainly is fitting today.
-Someone should've called me.
-I'm sorry.
Look, I know this can't
bring him back...
... but here, it's just a gesture.
Zoo dollars?
Yes, and come see the bird show
at 4. The macaws wear hats.
It's a lot cuter
if your monkey hasn't just died.
I know.
I can't believe Joey's having
lunch with his stalker!
What is she like?
You remember Kathy Bates in Misery?
Well, she looks
the exact opposite of that.
And she's not crazy?
Oh, no, no.
She's a total whack-job.
She thinks that Joey is
actually Dr. Drake Ramoray.
Oh, my God!
And he's going out with her?
He cannot pursue this.
Just because this woman sees Joey
through the magical box...
...in her living room
doesn't mean she's not a person.
Does she not deserve happiness?
Does she not deserve love?
Why are you looking at me? He's
the one who wants to boff the maniac!
Are you okay?
No. I'm just nervous.
Maybe if I just picture them all
in their underwear....
That's not a good idea. That's
the reason the last guy got fired.
I'm used to playing for grownups.
Grownups drink their coffee
and do their grownup thing.
And kids...
...Iisten.
It's just a huge responsibility.
What?
Are you gonna kiss me?
I was thinking about it.
Alrighty! Let's play some tunes!
Ok! Let's find some seats.
Chandle, we gonna find our seats.
Hold on a second.
He thinks he can.
Oh, what the hell.
He can.
-Hi, everybody. I'm Phoebe.
-Hi, Phoebe!
I'm gonna play some songs
about grandparents, okay?
Now Grandma's a person
Who everyone likes
She bought you a train
And a bright shiny bike
But lately she hasn't
Been coming to dinner
And last time you saw her
She looked so much thinner
Now your mom and your dad said
She moved to Peru
But the truth is she died
And someday you will too
I will have the great seven, and the doctor, will have the resertal.
-Oh, Drake, isn't it amazing?
-Yeah, it is.
What?
Well, here we sit, devil-may-care...
...and a while ago you were
reattaching Simone's spinal cord.
That was a tricky one.
In reality...
...that operation takes 10 hours.
But they only showed it for 2 minutes.
Who's "they"?
No one.
Drake, you are so talented.
Let me see those hands.
Oh, these hands,
these beautiful hands.
I could just eat them.
But I won't.
Otherwise my watch would fall off.
No, seriously.
These hands...
...these miracle, magical,
life-giving hands.
Just to be near them, touch them,
maybe even lick one?
All right. Just one.
You're good at that.
Oh, my God! Someone!
He's choking!
Is anyone here a doctor?
Yes, the best doctor in Salem!
Dr. Drake Ramoray!
Meet me in the nocturnal
house in 15 minutes.
Hey, look. I don't really enjoy
being with other men that way.
But, zoo dollars?
It's about your monkey!
It's alive.
I don't understand.
Why didn't you help that man?
Because I'm a neurosurgeon...
...and that was clearly a case of...
... "foodal chokage."
I gotta tell you something
You don't have to tell me anything.
You don't have to
explain yourself to me.
Who am I to question
the great Dr. Drake Ramoray?
I should be happy to be near you.
Hey, l
Hey what?
That's it. Just hey!
Like at the end of a dance. Hey!
There'll be times when you get older
When you'll want to sleep with people
Just to make them like you
But don't!
'Cause...
... that's another thing...
... that you don't wanna do
Everybody!
That's another thing
That you don't wanna do
-Excellent!
-Very informative!
Not at all inappropriate!
Thank you for coming, everybody!
There are cookies in the back.
That was great.
The kids loved you.
Yea! I rock!
And you know why?
Because you told the truth.
Nobody ever tells kids the truth.
You were incredible!
But...?
-How'd you know there was a "but"?
-I sense these things.
It was either "but" or "butter."
The thing is, I think
some of the parents...
...they were hoping that...
...you'd play more songs
about barnyard animals.
I can do that.
Really?
Because that would be fantastic!
What? You wanna kiss me?
I'm thinking about it.
So by the libery car carticuler, we still have some time.
What, I'm unemploy.
The bat.
Ambassador of darkness.
Flitting out of his cave
like a winged messenger.
Sightless specter of the macabre.
Buddy, my monkey?
Oh, yeah, right.
There was a break-in...
...a few months back.
Inside job.
Your monkey was taken.
The zoo told me
that my monkey was dead!
The zoo!
You believe everything
the zoo tells you?
That's the only thing
the zoo's ever told me.
Of course they'll say that!
They don't want the bad publicity.
It's all a great big cover-up.
Do you have any idea
how high up this thing goes?
That guy Lipson?
Lipson knows?
-Do you have idea who else knows?
-I only know Lipson.
Lipson knows, huh?
Hello, Mr. Possum.
Enigma of the trees,
upside-down denizen of the night.
-Taunting gravity
-Buddy, my monkey. My monkey?
Word on the street
When I say "street," I mean those
pretend streets here at the zoo.
Of course.
Your monkey found a new career...
...in the entertainment field.
That's all I know.
This is unbelievable!
So what is this information
worth to you, my friend?
Are you trying
to get me to bribe you?
Maybe.
But you already told me everything.
Check it out.
He actually is
the Monkeyshine monkey!
What'll you do?
I'm gonna call the beer company
and try to find him.
That's what I did
when I lost my Clydesdales.
Okay, hi again!
Hi, Phoebe!
Today, we're gonna start with
some songs about barnyard animals.
Oh, the cow in the meadow goes "moo"
Then the farmer hits him
And grinds him up
And that's how we get hamburgers
Now chickens!
Only you who can save her, Drake!
Damn it! I'm a doctor.
I'm not God!
There goes my whole belief system.
It's Erika.
Quick! Shut off the TV.
I wanna see what happens!
I get Leslie out of the coma
then we make out.
How can that be?
You were kissing Sabrina!
Rachel, it's a world
where Joey is a neurosurgeon.
Hey, Erika. Come in.
How did you get here so fast?
I just saw you in Salem.
Right, they choppered me in.
What's up?
You're having a little party too!
-ls she here?
-Who?
Sabrina. I know about you two!
I saw you today, kissing
in the doctor's lounge.
It's not what you think
You told me I was the only one!
All right, look.
That's it.
We shouldn't see each other anymore.
I should have told you
a long time ago...
... but I am not Drake Ramoray.
I'm not even a doctor. I'm an actor.
I just pretend to be a doctor.
Oh, my God! Do the people
at the hospital know?
Somebody wanna help me out here?
Oh, I know! I know!
Where am I?
University Hospital...
... where you've been
for the last 18 years.
How can you be here and there?
Because it's a TV show!
What are you getting at?
Nice girl, not great with concept.
I'm not Drake!
That's right!
He's not Drake. He's...
... Hans Ramoray, Drake's evil twin!
Is this true?
Yes! Yes, it is true!
And I know this...
... because he pretended
to be Drake to sleep with me!
And then he told me
he would run away with me!
And he didn't!
And you left the toilet seat up,
you bastard!
Is all this true?
Yes, I'm afraid it is.
You deserve much better than me.
You deserve to be with the real Drake.
He's the one you fell in love with.
Go to Salem. Find him!
He's the guy for you!
Oh, Hans!
Hans?
Hans!
Yo, evil twin!
Right. Goodbye, Erika.
Good luck in Salem.
Take care.
I'll never forget you, Hans.
All right.
The people who threw the water!
Helping you out!
Fired?
Why?
The library board got a lot
of complaints from parents...
...about the stuff in your songs.
I can't believe this is the libery!
-I mean, books, freespeech, newspapers on sticks.
-I know.
What about the kids.
Did you tell your board that
the kids want to hear the truth?
I see.
Maybe if you just played
some regular kiddy songs?
What do you want me to be?
Like some...
...stupid, big,
like, purple dinosaur?
You don't have to be Barney.
Who's Barney?
I tracked down Marcel and get this.
He's healthy, he's happy...
...and he's in New York filming
Outbreak 2: The Virus Takes Manhattan.
You're kidding!
-This is amazing!
-I know.
I finally get a part on TV,
and the monkey's making movies.
Rachel, I'm ready.
Excuse me. Is this where the
singing lady is, who tells the truth?
I guess that's me.
She's here!
Sometimes men love women
Sometimes men love men
Then there are bisexuals
Though some just say
They're kidding themselves
This is exciting! I haven't
seen my monkey in a year.
What, you never
look down in the shower?
I'm not allowed to make one joke
in the "monkey is penis" genre?
Back up, please.
Back up. Come on.
Excuse me.
Where can we find the monkey?
I'm sorry.
It's a closed set.
I'm sorry, you don't understand.
I'm a friend of his.
We used to live together.
And I have a time share
in the Poconos with Flipper.
There he is!
Hey! Buddy!
Marcel! Marcel!
In the jungle
The mighty jungle
The lion sleeps tonight
In the jungle
The mighty jungle
The lion sleeps tonight
Excuse me, this is a
Closed set. We know.
But we're friends with the monkey.
Good morning.
Look who I brought!
Your old friend, Harry Elafonte!
Whoa, dude. Burn!
I don't get it.
He seemed so happy
to see me yesterday.
Don't take it personal. He's under
pressure, starring in a movie and all.
How big of a star is Marcel?
In human terms? I'd say...
... Cybill Shepherd.
So you guys in the movie
or you just really paranoid?
Hey, Sal?
Jerry wants to know
if the monkey's ready.
Excuse me?
Jerry is the director?
Which one's he?
-The one in the director's chair?
-Gotcha.
Pheebs, walk with me.
Why am I walking with you?
We're just going over here
so that we can get away from...
...the horrible flesh-eating virus!
For the love of God, woman,
listen to me!
Is he looking? Is he looking?
-We've got a problem.
-Tell me.
I can't do Chris' makeup.
She refuses to acknowledge
her mustache.
-ls it bad?
-lt looks like her eyebrow fell down.
Unless we convince her
to let me bleach it...
...Van Damme will be
making out with Gabe Kaplan.
I'll talk to her.
I hate actors.
Nice camouflage. For a minute there,
I almost didn't see you.
Excuse me.
Is your name Chandler?
Yes, it is.
Chandler Bing.
Do you know me or are you
just really good at this game?
I'm Susie Moss.
Fourth grade? Glasses?
I carried a box of
animal crackers like a purse?
Susie Moss!
Right! Yeah! Wow!
You look....
Great job growing up.
It's nice to see you don't still
wear the cap with the mirrors on it.
I graduated fourth grade
and realized I wasn't a pimp.
Remember the class play?
You pulled up my skirt and the
entire auditorium saw my underpants?
Yes. Back then, I used humor
as a defense mechanism.
Thank God I don't do that anymore.
What you have been doing since childhood?
Well, I got a new belt.
I wondered!
-Oh, my God!
-What? What?
It's Jean-Claude Van Damme.
I didn't know he was in
this movie. He is so hot!
You think?
The Muscles from Brussels?
Wham-Bam-Van-Damme?
Did you see Time Cop?
No. Was he any good in it?
Rachel, he totally changed time!
So why don't you go talk to him?
Go tell him he's cute.
What's the worst that could happen?
He could hear me.
-I'm doing it for you.
-Don't you dare! Don't!
Don't!
Tell him I cook!
Excuse me.
This is gonna sound kind of goofy...
... but my friend over there...
...who cooks, by the way....
She thinks you're cute.
You don't think I'm cute?
I don't know.
Do you think you're cute?
We're getting off the track.
I was supposed to tell you...
... my friend thinks you're cute.
What should I tell her?
You can tell her
I think her friend is cute.
-Makeup!
-That's me. I gotta go.
How many times must I touch you on
the arm before you ask me on a date?
Well, let's try one more.
There you go. Ernie's, 8:00?
I'll be there.
And if things go well,
maybe this time...
... I'll get to see your underwear.
No one was around to hear that?
So what'd he say?
What a jerk!
I kept talking about you,
and he kept asking me out.
Naturally, you know, I said no.
Thanks, anyway.
He just kept asking...
...and asking, asking, asking....
If you want to go out
with him, you can.
Sounds like a jerk to me, but
Jean-Claude, she said yes!
I'll see you tonight!
Thank you.
Then Jean-Claude took me
to Crossroads...
...and we hung out
with Drew Barrymore.
Oh, man. She's so smokin'!
She's got the greatest set of
No guys around, huh?
-Does anybody need anything?
-I'll have an espresso.
I'll get it.
If I ask you to, you'll end up
drinking it yourself.
-That is so unfair.
-I know.
Like you'd drink her coffee after
what you did to her with Van Damme?
I have to cancel racquetball tonight.
Marcel's trainer will let me
have him for a couple of hours.
You're blowing me off for a monkey?
We can reschedule for Saturday.
Unless you hook up
with a bunch of pigeons.
Stick a fork in me...
... I am done!
Stick a fork what?
Like when you're cooking a steak.
I don't eat meat.
How do you know vegetables are done?
Well, you don't.
You eat them and you can tell.
Okay, then eat me, I'm done!
I've met the perfect woman.
We're sitting on her couch,
fooling around...
...and then she turns to me and says:
"Did you ever want to do it
in an elevator?"
What did you say?
I believe my exact words were....
How do you know if you wanna do that?
You just know.
We gotta go.
Got a reservation in 30 minutes.
What I had planned shouldn't take
more than two, three minutes, tops.
Two hundred seconds of passion!
We gotta go.
But...
... here's an idea.
Have you ever worn women's underwear?
Well, yes, actually...
... but they were my Aunt Edna's.
And there were three of us in there.
I was thinking
it would be kind of sexy...
...if you wore mine tonight
at dinner.
You want me to wear your panties?
Could you?
If I was wearing your underwear...
...then what would you be wearing?
You're swell!
Got the music, got the dinner.
I made Marcel's favorite dish,
banana cake...
...with mealworm.
Candle.
What do you think's
gonna happen here tonight?
Hi, are you on your way over
No, I understand.
A monkey's gotta work.
It's no big deal.
It's not like I had
anything special planned.
-You feel that?
-what?
We passed moment we should stop holding hands.
Rachel, why don't you
start talking first?
I feel that this is
totally unjustified.
She gave me the green light,
I did nothing
Do you think I can't
see you in the TV set?
If there's something
you'd like to share
You had no right to go out with him!
-That's the most ridiculous
-You sold me out!
-I did not!
-You absolutely
Would you let me talk!
Did you just flick me?
Well, you wouldn't let me
finish and I was
That hurt!
Quit flicking!
Stop flicking!
You flicked me first!
Let's not do this!
Happy thoughts!
Now I'm gonna kick some ass!
All right. Now, I will
let go if you both stop.
You want me to stop seeing him?
You want me to just tell him
you're seeing him instead?
Is that what you want?
That's what you want?
-Fine!
There we go.
If we were in prison,
you guys would be, like, my bitches.
Thanks for letting me tag along.
Forget about it.
How you doing there, squirmy?
I'm hanging in.
And a little out.
So assistant to the director?
That's an exciting job. You must
have a ton of responsibilities
I don't do the casting.
So what are you guys gonna eat?
How come all I can think about is
putting that ice in my mouth...
...and licking you all over?
Because I went to an all-boys high
school, and God is making up for it?
I want you right here...
... right now.
Right now, right here?
Don't you think we're in
kind of a public place?
They do have the shrimp.
Meet me in the bathroom.
I'm going to the bathroom now.
Come on.
All right, mister.
Let's see those panties.
Alrighty.
But you know what
would be even sexier?
What?
If you didn't have
your shirt tucked into them.
All right. Now, I would like
to see you wearing nothing but them.
Take your clothes off.
I hope you realize this means
we'll miss hearing about the specials.
Come on, hurry!
Do you want this done quick
or done right?
All right, turn around.
I wanna see you from behind.
Somebody's been doing
his Buns of Steel video.
So you want me
to clench anything or...?
Susie?
This is for the fourth grade.
-What do you mean?
-What do I mean?
What do I mean?!
I mean underpants, mister!
That's what I mean!
What? What do you mean?
My skirt...
...you lifted. IKids laughing!
I was Susie Underpants till I was 18!
That was in fourth grade!
How could you still be upset?
Call me in 20 years and tell me
if you're still upset about this.
I hope you realize you're not
getting these underpants back!
I can't believe this.
Just two weeks ago,
I was watching Sudden Death...
...and now I'm on a date
with Jean-Claude Van Damme.
Can you beat up that guy?
-Can you beat up that guy?
-Sure.
This is so wild.
I gotta admit, I was surprised
that you agreed to go on a blind date.
Normally, I would not do it.
What made you make
the exception for me?
Rachel told me...
...you were dying to have a threesome
with me and Drew Barrymore.
By the way, Drew has
some ground rules and....
Say you're sorry!
Say it!
No! I'm not gonna!
Say it! Say it!
Great!
Say you're sorry
or your sweater gets it.
That is my favorite sweater!
That is my third-date sweater!
Say you're sorry.
You wanna play?
Okay, let's play.
Let's play.
What'll you do?
Give me back my sweater
or it's handbag marinara.
You don't have the guts.
Yeah? At least I wasn't too chicken
to tell some guy he was cute.
Stop! Stop the madness!
This is crazy!
Who can remember why
you're fighting in the first place?
Yes, that's right.
But still....
Look at your purse!
Look at your sweater!
Look at yourselves!
I'll help you fix your sweater.
I'll help you...
...throw out your purse.
I'm sorry I made you stop seeing him.
I'm sorry I went out with him
when I knew you liked him.
I'm sorry that I borrowed your gloves.
Joey?
Ma?
What are you doing here?
I thought you guys took off.
She took off with my clothes!
-Are you naked in there?
-Well, not exactly.
I'm wearing panties.
You always wear panties?
No, no. This is the first time.
Talk about your bad luck!
The first time you try panties and
someone walks off with your clothes.
I was not trying them out.
Susie asked me to wear them.
Let me see!
No! I'm not letting you
or anybody else see, ever!
All right, all right!
Someone's flossing!
Joey, some people don't like that.
Chandler's wearing panties.
What?
-Let me see!
-You don't have to see!
Hi, tushy!
One of you give me your underpants.
I'm not wearing any.
How can you not be wearing any?
I'm getting heat from the guy
in the hot pink thong.
Look, Ross. I'll give you
$50 for your underpants.
-Can I have the milk?
-I'm almost done with it.
Keep your panties on.
And I'm in the movie!
-What happened?
-A virus victim called in sick...
...so Cathy recommended me and boom!
I'm dying on a gurney!
Marcel just finished his last scene,
if you wanna go say goodbye.
That's okay. He's probably
got parties to go to and stuff.
He's moved on.
That's the way it goes, right?
Oh, my God!
What?
Looks like we made it
Left each other on the way...
... to another love
Looks like we made it
Or I thought so, till today
Until you were there, everywhere
And all I could taste was
Love the way we made it
Looks like we made it
I'm sorry. It has work between you and me. Or you and me.
Drew was very disapoited.
Well, bye for me too.
Okay, we will bye-bye again.
Perhaps the three of us. Just...
Are you sure, I can crush longer with my butt.
No, no, no...Impressive but no.
Bye, Marcel!
See you on the big screen.
You keep people drinking that beer.
I will miss you buddy.
I think I want to write
a song about all this.
Except one of the strings
on my guitar is broken.
Chandler, can I borrow your G-string?
-How long you been waiting to say that?
-About 20 minutes!
Can't you see what's going on here?
This man is dying!
Cut!
Can't you see what's going on here?
This man is dying!
Cut!
Can't you see what's going on here?
This man is dying!
Mommy!
Can't you see what's going on?
This man is dead!